[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For some reason, you  are playing craps. The person rolling wants Little Joe. What is he hoping for?", "correct_answer": "a 4", "incorrect_answers": ["a 12", "a 2", "a 14"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Canada is by far the worlds largest maple syrup producer. Approximately what part of the worlds maple syrup is produced in Canada?", "correct_answer": "80%", "incorrect_answers": ["65%", "95%", "70%"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The diameter of the largest crater on the moon is 1,044 miles across.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In motion picture, Pulp Fiction, what kind of car does Winston Wolf drive?", "correct_answer": "Acura NSX", "incorrect_answers": ["Dodge Viper", "Lexus SC400", "Porsche 911 Speedster"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The terms sweating and steaming refer to one and the same method of cooking.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A shade of which color is the so-called June bud color?", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Orange", "Coral", "Pink"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what novel one of the main characters is a white whale hunted by a whaling ship?", "correct_answer": "Moby-Dick", "incorrect_answers": ["North Against South", "Twenty Thousand Leagues Under the Sea", "The Purchase of the North Pole"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What 1987 movie is this quote from: They can get to anyone, they can kill anybody. You want them to know who you are? Do you??", "correct_answer": "The Believers", "incorrect_answers": ["Dark Tower", "Hellraiser", "The Wind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress and comedienne won an Emmy Award for her satirical portrayal of Sarah Palin in a guest appearance on SNL?", "correct_answer": "Tina Fey", "incorrect_answers": ["Sarah Silverman", "Ellen DeGeneres", "Amy Poehler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of Shrek the Third, we see that Shrek becomes a father. How many kids does he have?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["4", "1", "2"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This country is the worlds largest exporter of corals.", "correct_answer": "Indonesia", "incorrect_answers": ["India", "Australia", "Thailand"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The surface area of the moon is 14,658,000 square miles.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]